Harish Nandhan G

Engineering Student

Personal Info

Phone

+91 9655326875

E-mail

harishtipsc@gmail.com

Skills

Adaptability

Customer Service

Programming(Java, Python, Flutter)

Microsoft Office

Effective Time Managment

Critical thinking and problem olving

Team leadership

Communications & Relation exert

Engineering design tools

Adavance Analytical Thinking S kill

Ability to Multitask

Fast Learner

Work Independently

Links

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/harish-nandhan-2a1a7792

Hobbies

Aiming to push boundaries in space travel & conventional thrust operations, through Electrodynamic Asteroid Tethering applications. In hopes of discovering and developing reusable deep space elements in an industry-beneficial combination matrix in the foreseeable future.

Presently, on the lookout for jobs requiring an insightful and effectual customer executive with 2+ years in the retail Industry, providing merchandise support, logistics help, finance logging assistance and other administrative work. Coordinated and adept in handling technical support.

Experience

Event Coordinator

Eventese / 04/2018 - 02/2020

Setting up event stalls for all entrepreneurial exhibits on a contract basis. Optimizing sales & customer experience spontaneously to rise product appeal. Experienced divisions include food, clothing, arts and crafts.

Best Sales award: Table's Worth and Blunch(Food stalls)

Junior App Developer

Kaptas Technologies / 06/2019 - 06/2020

Web designers specializing in product engineering for MSMe businesses. Integrated cloud-based Android applications development & Network Server Management.

Worked on an Event Management mobile app featuring Internal chat and news APIs from local channels(integrating test cases & module testing in Android Studio).

Customer Executive(Sales & Service)

Thavam / 04/2017 - 02/2018

A clothing retail store for women and kids, dealing in traditional & modern outfits.

Job responsibilities included shop opening and setup(stocks log check, billing tills operations check, visual merchandise apparel check), and resume primary role - handling CRM suite for the store and updating customers on availability of stocks through eletronic-means and Social Media Platform.

Education

IB Diploma Programme

The Indian Public School / 01/2018 - 11/2019 Cbe.IND

Career-led courses: Physical Sciences, Computer Science and Advanced Mathematics.

Mechanical Engineering

University of Leeds / 09/2021 - Present Leeds

Specializing in Propulsion Systems Design and Avionics, and application of Hyper-Sonics

Courses

Connected-Tech & Electronic Circuitry Architecture L3

BigBodhi Institutions / 01/2016 - 09/2018

AutoCAD(Mechanical)

CADD Centre / 01/2020 - 04/2020

- I love listening to songs composed inmy native language and replicating them on my guitar.
 Have a huge flair for Theatre Arts and Drama, interest caught on Helen O'Grady performances.
- Playing cricket and signing-up for adventure sports at scenic locations during travel&exploration.
- Partake in Forum & debates to address public administration matters.
- Working on Product Reverse Engineering, Robotics and UAV prototypes for pastime.

Lan	\sim		~~		_
1 411	ע		42	,,,	۰
EQI I	$\overline{}$	u	<i>~</i>	\sim	_

English	1		
Tamil			
Hindi			
French			

Certified SolidWorks Associate

SolidWorks Inc / 06/2023

Personal Project

Wireless Electronic System

04/2017 - Present

IND, UK

Developing applications for repetitive tasks using IoT with Raspberry Pi, Programmable Circuits Integration, Autonomous Drone systems & Mini Arduino projects.

Crypto Mining

05/2018 - 05/2018

Bitcoin mining using ASIC, redundant server hardware.

Freelance AutoCAD Engineer

Cadd / 04/2020 - 12/2020

Che.INC

Free Lance Product Development for MSME clients, designing universal tools and components.

Awards & Honours

ICE Award

09/2017 - 09/2017

Individual Sciences with Multilingual course completion

Trinity Awards

02/2017 - 10/2017

Grade 3 - Distinction (Both Theoritical and Instrumental)

FLL Designer Award

06/2016 - 06/2016

Robust, Ubiquitous Design

Top 3 in Module Integration

05/2015 - 08/2015

IRO

Robotics

High Achievers Award

01/2013 - 12/2016

TIPS

90th percentile in Assess360 performace evaluator

Youngest Material Fabricator

04/2015 - 05/2015

Building bicycle from scratch in the workshop

The Hindu TECHWIZ Qualifier Q1

05/2017 - 06/2017

Extreme Mountain Climbing

01/2018 - 01/2018

Himachal Pradesh

Climbed the Friendship Peak, located at 17,500ft

Diageo Hackathon Winner

06/2023 - 06/2023

London

Showcasing concept of an experience store with AI taste analyser

Agent of Change

07/2023 - 07/2023

Coimbatore

Tackling problems for Coimbatore Corp. in an initiative led by GDG Tech for Social